{
    "id": "42b24c52cc6e4e36a1b804c5d8f131d7",
    "title": "Some, Any, No, None | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "63c8284291a34e618131cb1608ac9421",
            "title": "Some, Any, None, No | Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "'Which dress should I wear?' '.............................. will do.'",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Any",
                        "Some",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you see .......................... parrots over there?",
                    "description": "Use any in questions and negatives use some in affirmative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "some",
                        "any",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'Are there ............................ apples in the fridge?'",
                    "description": "Use any in negatives and questions.",
                    "answers": [
                        "some",
                        "any",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The traveller asked for food but there was .............................. in the house.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "some",
                        "any",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He didn't show ............................ remorse.",
                    "description": "Use any in questions and negatives use some in affirmative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She doesn't have .............................. interest in politics.",
                    "description": "Use any in questions and negatives use some in affirmative sentences. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "no",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I have .............................. more coffee?",
                    "description": "Some is used in questions when we expect an yes for answer.",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has got hardly ................................. friends.",
                    "description": "Hardly any means more or less the same as no.",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has five children but ................................. of them lives with him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I called her in the afternoon but there was ................................. answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you receive .................................. information, let me know.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "none"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have never offered me ................................ help.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "some",
                        "no"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}